真是舒服呀，呢度好静呀？
Very comfortable, it's quiet here?
以前好旺的，点解而家冇硒人？
Used to be a crowded place, how come it's so quiet now?
唔知呀
I don't know
你看多漂亮，我想过对面呀
It's so pretty there, I want to get there
喂，你两个在干什么？
Hey, what are you two doing here?
在我地盘搞搞震，走唔走呀？
Damn you! You fool around in my site? Go away now
走啦
Beat it!
小心点呀
Be careful
死啦
Shit!
唔怕老实讲， 我而家正一系空心老倌啦
Frankly tell you, I am a man of none a penny
我所有资金，甚至毕生的积蓄
All my cash flow, even my savings
都投资硒在这个渡假村上面
has been invested on this resort village
翁Sir，我入纸申请旅游发展牌 足足一年
Officer Yung, I've applied for a resort licence for more than one year
消防条例，卫生条例， 游乐场安全条例
Regulations of Fire Department, Sanitary, and a playground regulations
我依到十足十，当然会挂万漏一
I've complied with them all, maybe I miss something
可能有少少唔合政府规格， 但系我一定改番好的
Which is not up to standard, but I'll improve whatever it is
我实在冇办法再等落去啦， 一年啦，我仲未有牌咼
I can't wait on any longer, it's one year and I still have no licence
Go卡呀日晒雨淋，全部散硒， 水塘干硒
The racing cars rust and the reservoir is dried out
气垫艇呢就扔下生绣了？
All the boats are rusting still
酒楼呀，Disco呀，，呕，，到发硒臭
The restaurants and discos are stink too
我本着为香港市民提供 廉价娱乐的目标
I at offering cheap entertainment for people of
投下毕生的精力心血， 换回来的系一盘烂帐
And I've invested all my money but what I get back rubble
搞到呢面临破产，我为了什么？
I'm nearly going bankruptcy! Why must I do this?
去炒楼咪算啰，我而家真系蠢啊
I should have invested in estate, I'm such a fool
你点会蠢呀，据我所知
No, you're not! As far as I know
你已经斟掂一个大陆财团， 收购你的渡假村啦
You're dealing with a Chinese group to sell your rest
照你当年买入的价钱同埋 而家卖番出去的价钱
On the price you bought in and the price you're selling
你赚的系天文数字咼
You'll surely make enormous profit!
翁Sir，你救救我，渡假村的 旅游牌照一日出唔到
Officer Yung, you must help me, one day I don't get licence
大陆班财团一日都唔肯出钱收购
The Chinese group won't buy the resort
俾息都俾到我摊摊腰呀
I'll be ruined just by paying interest
刘生你有咁多地， 咁多生意都唔驶怕？
Mr. Lau, you have much land and business, you needn't worry
我虽然系助理政务司， 都话得下事？
I'm Assistant Officer, I can still make decision
最可惜就系那些环保份子好麻烦
But those Conservationists are horrible
而且他们仲指明话你的 渡假村破坏环保添
They point out your resort is ruining the environment
我最近捐了笔钱俾环保呀
I've just donated a large sum for Conservative group
呢方面冇问题，只要翁Sir 大笔一挥，绝对冇问题？
It's no problem, as long as you sign it, it's surely
但系我支笔冇水咼
But I have no ink
冇问题咼，只要你批个牌俾我
It's no problem, if you will sign it
三十万呢，湿湿碎啦， 一定搞掂俾你
You'll get no less than $300,000
咁我下面支笔呢！
What about my pen under?
讲真啦，我好好奇呀， 都未试过明星
Frankly saying, I'm curious as I've never tried movie stars
NoProBLem，俥系我一手捧出的？
No problem, I've raised her to fame
我话Y es，俥唔敢话NO的，OK？
She will do whatever I ask her to?
好，既然你咁有诚意， 咁我即管试试帮帮你啦！
OK, since you're an honest man, I'll try to help you
咁就太好啦！
It's great!
听日呢，我就去伦敦开会
I'll be going for a meeting in London tomorrow
三日之后，我就去岛度见你
I'll be meeting you on the island in 3 days
好，一于包在我身上？
OK, you can count on me
多谢翁Sir！
Thanks, Officer Yung
阿芝呀，喂，阿芝呀， 你唔好行咁快啦
Chi, Chi... wait for me
你听我讲好唔好呀？
Will you listen to me?
我真系冇办法先至咁的， 咁你都唔帮我一次
I just couldn't help! You must help me this time
翁Sir唔错的，人又高大威猛， 又系政府官员咼
Officer Yung is good, he's strong and handsome, and officer too
既然你咁钟意俥，咪陪俥上床啰
As you like him, you might sleep with him
阿芝，我应承你，只此一次 下不为例，咁得了吧？
Chi, I promise, no more next time, OK?
喂，唔好嫐啦，你会嫐坏个样的
Don't be angry or you'll look ugly
你帮我呢一次， 渡假村顺利出了牌之后
Help me and if I get the licence for the resort
我买粒大钻石俾你？
I'll buy you a big diamond
你知唔知呀 我炒股呀蚀了几仟万
You know I lost millions of dollars in stock mark
事情搞不定，我跳楼的
I must die if I don't get a licence
讲钱，我都帮你媪唔少生意啦
You mention of money? I've helped you earn so much
你直情当我公厕咁， 边个急就媪边个
You take me as a toilet! Let whoever needs uses me
喂，你咁的态度算什么呀
Hey, what manner is this?
接几部烂鬼戏，就当自己系大明星
You think you're a superstar?
你记唔记得当年呀， 我在大陆点样对你屋企人呀！
Do you remember how I treated your family in China
我花几多钱同你包装整容
And I've spend so much to dress you up?
我对你好你就唔记得， 净系记得我的衰？
You forget all my good deeds to you but remember that little request?
你而家好巴闭啦
You're very smart now!
我都跟了你咁耐啦， 什么都还番硒俾你啦
I've been with you so long, so I've paid back everything
你仲想点咼
What do you still want?
你而家唔好同我讲咁多， 我唔理你制唔制都好
I don't care so much, whether you will or not
你都要做的啦，好好的， 打理下个身体
You must do it! Do care for your health
等翁Sir在英国回来的时候， 好好地服侍俥
That you can serve Officer Yung well when he comes back from UK
做乜呀，我同你讲话做乜 唔睬我呀！
Why? Why don't you answer me when I talk to you?
话你两句就扮硒鱼虾蟹， 重俾雷劈添，天收你呀
You behaved badly! That's why thunder struck you
大佬呀，唔关我事的，我系救俥的
Hey, I'm only trying to rescue her
大镬
Shit!
为了唔浪费刘先生的宝贵时间
In order not to waste your time, Mr. Lau
我会扼要介绍本医务所的优点
I'll briefly introduce advantages of our clinic
唔驶讲都知呀，刘先生咁精明
You surely know, Mr. Lau
我们系消费者委员会推荐 的三大整容医务所
We're one of the 3 clinics recommended by Consumer Council
不过唔讲你唔知咼， 内部评分我们系最ToP？
But you don't know, we're the top of the 3
同类型手术，好似整鼻隆胸呀咁
With plastic surgery, like breast enlargement
虽然同样收费呀， 但系我有保养维修服务
Tough we change the same, we have guarantee service
年费呢只系收全部费用的10%？
It service charge is only 10% of surgery fee annual
仲可以分期付款添， 不过以刘先生的身家地位
So with installment system, but you don't need that
梗系唔需要啦，至于眼耳口鼻
And about other parts, like eyes, ears, mouth, nose
胸，腿，手指，脚指都可以买保险
Or breasts, legs, fingers, all can come with insure
燕梳方面呢，我们免费代顾客安排
And we don't charge anything for that
而款式方面呢，全部都系欧洲， 瑞士同埋日本入口
All parts are imported from Switzerland and Japan
时装最ToP就系法国意大利
Yes, France and Italy is famous for fashion
整容呢当然就系瑞士同埋日本啦
But for surgery part, Swiss and Japanese is the best
我最大的优点呢，就系追得上潮流
I'm famous for following the trend
单方面为人客整鼻隆胸， 已经系落后的观念啦
Only surgery for nose and breasts is out-dated
我会为人客由头整到落尾， 由前整到落后
What I offer is of whole body
提供完整的Design，配合俥的性格
I offer a design unique for individual client
仓刂造完美的面貌
So as to create a perfect face for them
而且我系唔收Design费用添
Well, I don't charge the fee for design
如果系咁样我靠硒你了
I just totally rely on you No problem!
刘生，你睇版先啦， 之后我扼要解释俾你听
Mr. Lau, look at the samples and I'll explain
刘生，呢个日本最新的产品
Mr. Lau, this is latest products from Japan
系水剂，完全冇副作用的
It's water base, absolute without side effects
怀孕生仔，哺乳 能力一切正常， 软淋淋
One can even breed and feed babies, very soft
至于整鼻哥下巴最新的手术呢
And for nose and chin surgery
系由口内牙肉开刀出去， 完全不留痕迹
We start from inner jaw, so no scar is left
整鼻哥系由上牙肉开刀， 整下巴系由下牙肉开刀
Start from upper jaw for\and lower one for one
即日出院，双眼皮，割眼袋， 容易到极啦！
I can leave the clinic the same day! For eye surge it's even simpler
几个字就搞掂硒！
Just a couple of minutes and it's done
整容我都好熟行， 我女朋友整过好多次啦
Familiar with plastic surgery as my girlfriend had it lots of time
你睇睇俥先啦
Take a look of her first
好.
Sure...
除低面纱俾我睇？
Take the veil away
老老实实啦，俥真系好肉酸咼
I must warn you： she's really horrible
几肉酸我都见过啦， 我唔惊的，你放心啦
I've seen all faces, I won't fear, don't worry
唔驶怕丑，我帮你手
Don't be shy, I'll help you
都仲系好靓，以张小姐？ 面貌呢，烂船都有三斤钉
Not bad, with Miss Cheung's beauty, she'll still lot pretty
不过唔需要三斤啦，两斤半就够硒
She'll absolutely look good at the worst
我可以帮俥整到十全十美
I can help her look perfect
刘生，你唔系同我开玩笑嘛？
Mr. Lau, are you kidding?
呢个真系张小姐吗？
She's really Miss Cheung?
你唔认得俥咩？
Don't you recognize her?
认得下啦，不过搅成咁， 算小弟无能为力
Yes, but I can't help in this situation
咁你又话两斤半钉都得？
But you said she'll look good at the worst?
本来就系的， 唔该你关番面纱先，唔该你
Put on the veil first
关番面纱先啦
Put on the veil
医生点呀，有冇得医呀？
Doctor, can you perform operation?
你都唔系叫我整容， 叫我易容咼，唔得？
This is not plastic surgery, this is disguise, no way
我多多钱都俾得的，你惗惗俥？
I can pay whatever price you charge, think it over
得，你去媪司空摘星啦， 俥的易容术出神入化的
Yes, go find See Hung Chak Sing, he's famous for that
去边度媪呀
Where can I find him?
古龙的小说嘛， 陆小凤的好朋友，千面神偷呀
In fiction, he's famous for disguising
陈果大师呀 饮番杯陈年拔兰地酒先
Master Chan, taste this age-inconnu cognac
唔该你帮帮忙，医我女朋友啦
Please help and cure of my girlfriend
呢只不适合我饮的， 试试我呢只陈年秘方大补酒吧
It's not my cup of tea, try the wine I prepare
试试啦，呢只酒呀， 浸了百几年啦！
Try it, it's been kept for more than a century
试了一定会喜欢
饮啦！
Cheers!
正呀！
Excellent!
饮啦，饮完之后呀，包你，，发发，，声
You'll feel wonderful after drinking it
我呢个锦衣授魂术呢
About my skill of 'Changing Face'
系我祖宗一二三四五六七八九十 年代传俾我？
Was handed down from my remote ancestors
系我一个人先至识的
I'm the only person in this world who knows it
但系呢个秘方呢，系需要大量.
But this secret skill requires much...
钱唔系问题
Money is no problem
钱系第二个问题， 最紧要系媪个皮肤幼滑
They is only second problem, but I need a girl with delicate skin
年青貌美的少女， 将俥的青春转嫁俾俥
Pretty face so as to transfer her beauty to her
讲就容易咋咼，但边度媪呢？
It's easy to say, but where to find such one?
重有呀，呢对波呢， 大又唔可以太大
And her breasts mustn't be too big
腿呢，幼又唔可以咁幼
Her legs mustn't be too narrow either
呢个就系问题啦， 不过唔系我问题咼
This is the problem, of course not mine
系你的问题， 你呢就要抽点时间帮我
It's your problem, you must find time to help me
媪一个我需要的人，带俥来呢度
咁呢，我就可以保证恢复 番你女朋友原来的面貌啦
Then I can guarantee you of resuming her beauty again
小姐呀，你留低个电话呀
Miss, you've left your phone
唔该！
Thanks
阿嫂，番去先啦
Please go home first
唔返呀
I won't
阿嫂呀
Sister-in-law!
行开
Get lost
番去啦
Go home first
要番你咪自己番啰
You might go home!
走开呀
Beat it!
阿嫂你去边度呀，阿嫂？
Where are you going?
唔关你的事呀，唔驶你理
None of your business
咁点同大佬讲
What shall we say to the boss?
行啦
Move now
衰男人，贱男人， 臭男人冇个有良心
Lousy guy, you damned guy are disloyal
全部都系死铲
All men are damned fools
做什么呀，你个四眼佬， 你敢有尔我
What? Dare you touch me?
你知唔知我系边个， 我尖沙嘴霞姐你都敢有尔
Do you know who I am? I am Sister Ha of TST
你信唔信我一分钟之内 媪二百几人来劈死你个死铲
I can call 200 men here in 1 minute and kill you
王八蛋有尔手有尔脚
Dare you molest?
放开我
Let me go
你摸我个波，唔俾钱想搏懵， 你个衰佬放开我
You grasp my breasts? Leave me alone, bastard
做什么呀，放手呀
What are you doing? Let me go
你信唔信我媪人来阉了你，放开我
Must I have you castrate? Let me go
仆卜你个街
Go to hell!
望咩呀，未见过麻甩佬小便呀
Why? Haven't you seen a man piss before?
就算我唔杀俥呀， 俥迟早都横尸街头
She'll die one day if I didn't kill her
真系冇眼睇呀
It's too bad
阴气逼人
Full of spirit atmosphere
等我来个壮阳抗阴先
I must resist with human atmosphere
拿神盐俾我！
Get me the Sacred Salt
神盐呀
Sacred Salt
呢个岛风水好差， 所以搞到你几乎破产
This island is bad at Feng Shui, so you nearly go bankruptcy
呢个接近港岛的龙气， 可以镇住冤魂
This is good for your luck, as it damps furious ghosts
大师呀，俥会唔会变僵尸的
Master, will it become vampire?
唔会，系惊俥会尸变， 所以用倒转乾坤葬尸法
No, but I fear it'll become angry ghost, so I bury upside down
不过三日之内随时会变厉鬼
But it might become angry ghost within 3 days
咁大师呀，咁点呀？
What shall we do, master?
脚底块宝镜会反射月光的阴气
The Sacred Mirror on the feet reflects moonlight
俥而家做鬼都唔灵呀
It can never become a mighty ghost
将沙盖住盐，呢条尸剥硒皮
It's cover the salt with sand, as it's skinned off
最怕就系盐的啦，我已经洒了神盐
It fears salt most, I've sprinkled Sacred Salt over
而家有事的啦，呢三日 我会做法事超渡冤魂
lt'll be OK, and I'll perform ceremony for it for 3 days
三日之后毁尸灭迹
And we'll destroy the body in 3 days
那时候，你就可以高枕无忧啦！
Then you can be ease off forever
大师，咁我信硒你了
Master, I depend on you
希望搞掂啦，如果唔系呀， 我跳楼都唔掂的
I hope so, or I must die
洗钱就事小呀， 最紧要呢就系搞得妥妥当当
Money is nothing, I just want it done perfectly
你放心啦，包保你冇事的
Don't worry, it'll be alright
你做咩呀？
What are you doing?
大师，咁大整蛊呀
Master, what ajoke!
咩整蛊呀，俥刚刚做完法事
I'm not joking, it's just received my ceremony
吸收紧人皮锦衣的精华， 需要一段时间慢慢吸收
And it's now absorbing the skin, it takes time
人皮锦衣系至阴之物， 我话过要做三日法事
As the skin is from dead body, I must perform ceremony
一则超渡个冤魂， 二则消除俥身上的冤气
First to help the ghost and to rid spirit atmosphere attached on her
而家掂俥，或者口气喷亲俥
If you touch her or blow on her
俥身上的阴气被阳气一冲
All the spirit atmosphere will be blown off
咁会点呀？
What will happen?
玩完咯
Ruined!
两日唔上呢我就跳楼啦
I must die if it isn't done in 2days
咁你放心，两日之后俥自然会醒
Don't worry, she'll wake up in 2 days
疤痕自然会消失？
And all scars will vanish too
过瘾呀
Interesting!
请师祖回宫
Ancestor, please go back
多谢师祖
Thanks, ancestors
好劲呀
Terrific!
系咪想学呀，想学就拜师啦
Want to learn? Ask Master if you want
系呀
Yeah
十二，他们来做乜的？
Sup Yi, why are they here?
师父呀，我上次都讲过的啦， 系我的Friend来的
Mentor, I've told you, they're my friends
小妖同埋阿东，他们想拜 你为师呀，喂叫师父啦
Su Yi and Tung, they want you to take them as students greet the mentor now
师父！
Mentor!
咪住，你两个话俾我听
Hold it, you must tell me
你们学神功系为了什么？
Why do you want to learn Sacred Skills?
锄强扶弱！
To help the weak
除暴安良！
To rid the gangs
讲真话！
Tell me the truth
方便劈友
To have power
劈人唔怕俾人劈啰
I can chop others without being chopped
唔系劈人， 就算你俾人劈都唔怕的啦
Not chopping, you needn't fear to be chopped
请神呀，就等于练了金钟罩的啦
Inviting Gods mean having protecting all over
系好过金钟罩呀， 练金钟罩要童子身的嘛
It's even better than practicing, as one must be virgin to practise
你们可以唔沟女咩，重有呀
So you mustn't court girls
十二，话俾他们听， 学神功最紧要系乜？
Sup Yi, tell them what's most important when learn Sacred Skills
最紧要准时交学费嘛
Most important is to pay school fee punctually
死的
Shit!
驶乜你讲咼， 学神功呢最紧要系诚心诚意
You needn't say that, one must be honest when learn Sacred Skills
千万唔好半途而废呀
And never drop out
约了班女呀，第日先拜师啦
I have appointment with girls, we'll come other time
师父呀，第日择好日子， 再来拜师呀
Mentor, we'll come when we've found a good day
我们走先啦！
We're leaving now
你唔记得我讲过乜？
Do you remember what I've said?
诚心诚意嘛
One must be honest!
记得交学费呀
You must pay fee punctually
我条女呀话媪了两个 姐妹出来咼，够Friend呀
My girl said she'd ask two other girls out
小妖那件呢就细细粒
Elf will get a short one
十二那件就老处， 高头大马，波大大？
And Sup Yi will get a tall one, with big breasts
你知唔知呀，我绰号叫乜？
Do you know what my nick name is?
我绰号叫，，情场罐头刀，，
It's 'Girl Opener'
死啦你，而家兴易拉罐的， 开罐头驶乜罐头刀咼
Shit, girls are open now, they don't need you
老死先话俾你听， 你把刀，听生绣都得啦
I'll tell you, your weapon is rusting
玩我系嘛
Dare you fool me?
系咪约了十二同小妖呢！
You have an appointment with Elf?
系呀，那晚落完D之后成日问长问短
Yeah, you keeping asking about him after that night
早知你吃硬俥啦， 你钟意十二嘛，系咪？
So you like Sup Yi, right?
一场姐妹，费事同你争啦
I won't seize him from you
我蚀底点，就拣小妖啦
OK, I'll take Elf
呢次就系你抅失身的好机会啦
It's your good chance to lose your chastity
失身！你讲呀，我都唔记得几时啦
Chastity? I lost it long ago
Wancy，乜你仲系老处咩？
Wancy, you're still virgin?
发达啦，戏真情假，多情善忘
Great, it's good acting like this
最紧要呢就系有性冇爱
lmportant is to have sex only
喂，仲有乜招数呀？
What skills do you have?
最紧要HaPPy，不过就唔要BaBy
I want to be happy but no baby
胶袋你？，仔好懒
This condom is for you, guys are lazy now
他们不带就不行啦
If they forget this, it'll spoil the mood
不过今次一定要吊下俥瘾先啦， 大家要忍一忍啦
But we must hang on them for a while, we must bear If not, they'll find us cheap
如果唔系，我们就唔吃香的啦！
It's hard to bear? How long must we bear?
好难顶的，，，High，，阵要忍几耐先
Just one night
忍一晚
Are you kidding?
你讲呀
Hey, that guy is staring at us
喂，个胡须仔眼超超咼
Is it done?
喂搞掂未呀？
Time's short! Must I help you out?
好赶呀，走先啦， 驶唔驶我帮你避呀
It's troublesome! Let's go
真系麻烦啦，行啦行啦，出去啦
Hey, guy, have you started at me enough?
喂胡须仔，睇咁耐仲未睇够呀
你恨到啦，胡须仔
You like this, guy?
食蕉啦！
Screw yourself!
阿东，女呢，船都埋岸好耐啦
Tung, where're the girls? The ship has embarked already
系咪老点的？
Is she fooling you?
俥敢点我，俥唔惊我飞起俥呀
She dare not as she fears I desert her
话飞边个呀，唔系话我呀
You desert her? You mean me?
我的Friend，Wancy，Mueue 见过啦
My friends, Wancy, Mueue, you've met already
咁迟的你
Why are you so late?
系咪咋型先，系咪走啰！
You're complaining? We'll leave then
你重咁屎忽鬼， 今晚我就扌卜镬劲的你
If you behave badly, I'll screw you hard tonight
你话扌卜就扌卜，你当我木鱼呀
What? You take me as a whore?
平时又话自己系大男人， 原来系小男人
You always say you're big man! Just small man only
好，我依家就扌卜你
OK, I'll screw you off now
好呀，扌卜我啦.谁怕谁
Good, come on...
扌卜到你闩唔到水喉
I must screw you until you die
开船啦，走啦！
Set sail now, let's go
喂，小妖呢袋你的，拿住
This bag is for you, take it
死吧
有冇搞错呀，想谋杀咩？
Why? You want to kill me?
撞鬼你咩
What happens to you?
做乜你，扮硒款，，惭，，有型咁
Why do you pretend to be stately?
系呀，你估你们系，，Mark，，哥呀？
Yeah, you think you're bosses?
唔系Mark哥，船头尺
你似周润发？
You mean you look like movie star?
错，唔系周润发， 系周星驰个Friend周星星呀
No, we look like superstar
三位俏娇娃，趁大家咁高兴
As we're so happy
等小弟呢唱番只歌你听
Let me sing you a song
唱乜歌呀，想唱沉只船咩
Which song? I don't want to die yet
我蚀底点，表演神打俥睇？
Let me show you my Sacred Skills
神打？你得唔得呀？
Sacred Skills? Can you?
咩唔得呀，在船就未试过
Sure, not never on a boat before
等俥表演澿神打摧童术俾你睇啦
Let him show you how to invite Gods here
摧童？你吹牛咋
Invite Gods? You're boasting!
唔信系咪，好，两位师弟埋位
You don't believe? Colleagues, come here
系
Yes
我们拜师祖先
Let's worship ancestors first
都冇香
Is there incense?
系啰，冇香点拜呀？
Yeah, how to worship without incense?
我们唔驶香？
We don't need incenses
我们心中有香，胜过千言与万语
We have incenses in our mind, come on
想偷窥？
You peep at this time?
师祖显威灵
Ancestor, show your power
死仔呀唔好弄烂我只船呀仆卜街
Bastard, don't damage my boat
师祖显威灵
Ancestor, show your power
占童！
Gods come!
喂，咁玩法有冇事的？
Is it alright by playing this?
你们睇啦
You can see
仲玩系嘛
Still fool on?
师祖回宫
Ancestor, go back please
俥占乩童上身，赶唔走呀
God is possessing him, it won't go away
我要大打东海龙皇
I must stir up the sea
老师祖回宫
Ancestor, go back now
点呀，放低先啦
Lie down first
最衰十二呀，成日搅搅震
Sup Yi is bad, he always starts trouble
都叫你唔好玩的啦， 唔好再玩这些东西了
I've asked you not to play, stop doing this again
你估人家想的咩
He doesn't want this either
离谱，搅成俥咁
Shit, look how he is now
阿伯，你点呀？
Old man, how are you now?
冇事
I'm fine
多谢你呀，伯伯
Thanks, Old Man
后生仔，唔好同神打开玩笑呀， 好危险的
Kids, don't fool with gods and fairy
我知系我唔好？
I know I am to blame
荒山野岭，好多污糟的， 我比度符你旁身啦
Spirits are everywhere in this remote place, I'll give you a spell
戴住俥啦
Put it on
阿伯，你点呀？
Old Man, how are you?
我同你戴啦
I'll put it on for you
真系多谢你呀，阿伯
Thanks very much, Uncle
到啦
Here we are
快点啦.
Hurry...
行快点啦
Walk faster...
等埋呀
Wait for me
等一阵先
Wait
多谢阿伯救命之恩.拜拜
Thanks for saving me... bye!
等埋我呀
Wait for me!
阿娣，我们终于都番到啦， 我唔会再走
Tee, we've come back at last, I'll never go away again
过来呀，打波啦，过来呀
Come and play ball games, come on
快点呀
Come quick
打波呀好啊
You want ball games?
系唔系打波呀？
Let's play games
打波呀
乜个沙滩咁多波的？
Why are there so many balls here?
十二就好啦，Wancy索俥个鼻
Sup Yi is enjoying as Wancy is kissing his nose
Wancy自己发姣之嘛， 上次已经喜欢十二啦
Wancy is mad for him, she loves him much
咁你几时索我个鼻呀？
When will you kiss my nose?
鬼索你个鼻呀
I won't kiss your nose
点解你唔问我呀？
Why don't you ask me?
你又几时索我个鼻呀
When will you kiss my nose then?
睇下点
It depends
打情骂俏咁话咼
You're flirting?
你做乜呀？
What are you doing?
做乜？，冇事呀，边有事冇事呀
Nothing? I'm doing nothing at all
你做乜？
What are you doing?
急尿呀
I have natural call
急尿咪去后面啰
Go there if you must
你自己番去先啦
You might go back now
你做乜呀，你怕丑呀， 你咪后面啰
Why? You're shy? Just piss there
我又唔会装你？
And I won't peep
好呀
OK
做乜呀？
What's on?
我整亲只手呀，你仲唔快过来睇我
I've hurt my hand, come and take a look
点呀？
How is it?
你睇，流血啦
Look, it's bleeding
痛唔痛呀？
Does it hurt?
唔驶惊冇事的
Don't panic, it's going to be fine
21，22，2324，成日咼
21, 22, 23, 24, it's a whole day now
24小时仲未搞掂，，，及及，，先啦
Not yet done for 24 hours? I must take a look
小心踢爆
Watch out
我已经话过做法事阵唔可以入房啦
I've told you not to enter when I'm performing ceremony
好在落在本门守护降
Lucky I have put a protecting charm
大师呀， 你做了二十几个钟头法事的喇
Master, you've performed it for a whole day
我约了高官交人的，大师呀
I've promised an officer to hand her to him, master
你救救我啦，我死人跳楼的喂
You must help me or I must die
拮你.
Pin you...
子孙根，别乱插
喂.唔好玩啦
Hey... let's not play
都话唔好玩啰
Come on, I've said not to play
等我讲故仔俾你听， 你们知唔知道呀
Let me tell you, you don't know
呢个沙滩呀好猛鬼的
It's said this is a haunted beach
听老人家讲呢，呢个沙滩
Local people keep saying
以前系日本仔用来杀人的地方
Chis used to be the place for execution by Japanese
那些日本仔， 用铁线将人呢全部拍埋
Japanese soldiers tied people together with a wire
排成一排排
And made them fall in line
咁用铁线呢穿过他们身
And used wire to pierce them in a queue
监生等他们挣扌匕到死为止咼， 成行成群
And let them struggle until death
成个沙滩都系人，咁跟住呢
The beach was crowded with people and then...
在十几年前，有两个人咼， 系一男一女？
A decade ago, one guy and a girl
咁他们在这里露营咼， 就在而家呢个位置呀
Came here for camping, exactly at this position
咁俥睡觉啦，睡到差唔多大约 三四点的时候
They were sleeping but at about 4 am
忽然之间，他们听到些声咼
They suddenly heard some noise
咁他们拉开个帐篷啦
So they pulled the tent open
见到好多人在这里呀
And saw many people here
个个着住清装的， 拿住灯笼行来行去
All were dressed in Ching Dynasty clothes and holding a lantern
他们惊起上来， 即刻走去码头那边啦
They were so scared that they ran towards the piece
咁就撞到两个水警咼， 点知行到埋去就唔见？
And met two marine policemen, who vanished when the approached
咁他们好惊啦，咁即刻走番转头啦
They were so scared and ran back
咁就走番去营幕那边， 点知唔见硒人
They got back to the tent but nobody was there
咁他们见到衫，全部都湿硒？
And all their clothes were wet
咁于是呢咁就系咁扭啦
So they twisted them
点知扭出来的不是咸水，系淡水
What came out was not sea water, but just water
咁跟住呢又见到个女人咼， 系个女鬼
And soon they saw a girl, or rather a girl ghost
咁呢只女鬼呢，俥头发好长的
It was a ghost with long hair
咁着住件白袍，又好长的咼
In a long white robe
在这里行来行去，行到去沙滩那边
Who kept walking about, and she went to the beach
咁跟住呢，又行去后面
And then walked to the back again
哗，你睇？
Hey, look!
死小妖，仆卜街玩我？
Elf, dare you fool us?
搞掂，发达咯
It's done, great!
毒蛇缠呀，你两个过来帮拖呀
You two come back and help me
喷她.
Let's not play
湿完了
Elf keeps fooling us around, look
唔玩啦
Shit, it's sticky all over, what shall we do?
小妖成日扮鬼扮马整蛊人，你睇？
I'm sticky too, dare you swim nakedly?
咪啰，整到周身笠笠， 你睇而家点算啦
Sure, why not?
我够搞到笠笠啰， 够唔够，，poP，，一齐裸泳？
You say so, let's go
惊乜，裸泳咪裸泳啰
Why? You said you'd swim naked?
你讲的，去啦
Don't push me
喂玩呀，又话裸泳
Yeah
要除衫呀，催催贡
Take off your clothes... be quick
系呀
Great!
喂，除衫啦除衫啦，快啦
Something to see
正呀
Shit, you fool me!
睇啦，睇硒啦
I'll get dressed
媪笨，蚀底硒添呀
They made us sticky all over, nut!
着番衫先啦
Where are you going?
俾班死仔搞到成身笠笠，衰人
Get water for a bath, I won't swim naked with you
喂，你们去边度呀？
There's ghost up there, aren't you afraid?
媪淡水冲凉啰， 唔通真系同你们裸泳呀
There're 3 devils of you down here
上面有鬼的咼，你唔惊呀
Nothing to fool now
下面够有鬼啰，有你三只咸湿鬼呀
Let's go
冇东西玩啦
It's horrible up there, is there really a ghost?
走啦
You're timid? You're afraid?
上面咁恐怖，系咪真系有鬼的
Let's help you out
咪咁细胆啦，好惊呀
Don't be afraid
等我们帮你啦
Why touch my ass? Hands off
唔驶惊咼
I'm only helping you up
做乜摸我椤柚呀，放手呀
You're trapping my underwear
我帮手托你上去嘛
You're fat bottomed, it's hard to push up
你隙住我条底裤啦
You're caressing or pushing? I can't help caressing, get up there!
你个椤柚咁重呀，托极都唔上？
Very elastic
椤柚翘起，唔摸唔俾面呀，上去啦
It's done
够硒弹力
Listen, you 3 devils mustn't follow us on
搞掂
No, but there's really a ghost up there
听住呀，你们三只咸湿鬼 唔好再跟住来呀
Very furious ghost!
喂，唔系咼，上面真系有鬼的
It's said women's underwear can cast ghosts away
好猛鬼的！
Damned shit!
听讲女人底裤真系治邪的
Let's go and scare them
治你老母呀
Sure
一于上去吓俥
Let's get up, good!
好呀
This way
喂，上去呀，好呀
Must we take them off?
呢便呀
Sure, we must believe it
系咪真系要除的
OK, let's take it off
除啦，宁可信其有，不可信其无
除就除啦
Hurry up!
快点啦
边度的，好惊呀
Where is it? I'm afraid
好声呀
Be careful!
好恐怖呀呢度
It's terrifying here
究竟是边？
Where is it exactly?
喂，上去先媪啦
Hey, let's find up there
等埋我呀
Wait for me
喂，有个水井在这里咼
Hey, there's a well here
系咼
Yeah
不过有冇水的？
But is there water?
丢个桶落去咪知
We'll see if we throw a bucket down
小心？
Be careful
得啦
I will
有水
There's water
好啊
Great
好啊，唔使腌咸鸡啦
Good, we needn't stay dirty
咁重，几多水咼个井
It's heavy, the well is full of water
静静，行啦
Let's move quietly
喂，Micelle，得未呀？
Hey, Michelle, is it OK?
来啦
Coming
喂，放我出来.
Let me out...
你班仆卜街，装我们冲凉
Bastards, dare you peep us bathing?
Micelle，快澿水，快澿啦！
Michelle, get water here, quick
水啦
Here comes the water
你做乜？，放我出？
What are you doing? Let me out
系呀！抵你有今日，未死过
You deserve this, lousy
放我出来啦
Let me out...
唔好再淋啦
Don't splash anymore
淋死你？
Drown you
大师，你在这里做什么？
Master, what are you doing?
数钱啰
I am counting money
这时候仲数银纸
You count money at this critical moment?
食早餐先啦
Let's eat breakfast
一日三餐，最紧要就系早餐， 来啦，一齐食啦
Breakfast is most important to man, let's eat now
唔驶客气啦
Thanks
这些老鼠刚刚地牢捉番， 即杀即炸，好新鲜的
I've just caught and fried the mice, very fresh
我而家食龙肉都冇用啦， 阿芝点呀，冇时间啦
I have no appetite at all, how is Chi now?
我下昼约了人
I've an appointment this afternoon
有时间，醒了啦，你自己落去睇
Time is good, she's waken up, go and take a look
系
Yes
刚刚好
Time is good
喂，老头，我媪蒙你好耐啦
Hey, I've looked for you for a long time
点呀，间屋卖唔卖呀？
Are you going to see the house or not?
喂，我有个好大的旅游计划进行
I have a huge project to start here
而家你咁样阻住个地球转
But you're hindering it like this
喂，当我俾面你啦， 你到底要几多钱先肯卖
OK, how much will you take to sell it?
我唔等钱驶
I don't need money
喂.我而家俾到一千蚊你咼， 你仲唔满足
Hey... l'm already offering you $1000, you're still not satisfied?
你唔理我嘛，到时我节断 硒你的水电
Soon I'll cut off your water and power supply
周围围硒墙，睇你点样生活
And set up walls around, I'll see how you live on
到时你呃我，我都唔比你的
Then I won't pay you a dollar even if you beg me
你有病呀？
Are you sick?
你讲咩呀？
What do you mean?
你六神无主，印堂发黑
You look bad
如果唔系有病，就一定系 煞星缠身，你小心点
If you're not sick, then you run into devil, watch out!
喂，老鬼，你咒我， 到时四面围硒墙呀
Old bag, dare you curse me? When walls are set
你唔慌唔煞星缠身呀
I'll see if you're running into devil?
翁Sir，欢迎.
Officer Yung, welcome...
Cheers -Cheers
Cheers! D! D! D
食吧.
Let's eat...
Sorry，我有个长途电话要打
Sorry, I must make a long distant call
好好地服侍人，乖乖地
Serve the officer well, be good
我们饮杯
Cheers
我次次玩女人都唔使钱， 自动有人送上门的
I needn't pay when I fool with women, they come by themselves
喂.今晚咩环境，禽晚 我已经吊了他们成晚瘾
Hey... what about tonight? We did hand them around last night
仲使讲，今晚梗系自由发挥啦
You can do whatever you want tonight of course
早就知你姣婆守唔到寡
I know you will flirt early
彼此.
You the same...
食得未呀！
Is it ready?
点呀，十二食得未呀！
How is it? Sup Yi, is it cooked?
墨鱼丸好正的，你睇？
The squid balls smell good, look...
好香呀，仲有香肠
Tasty, there're sausages too
烧靓点咼
Make it good
净系识得烧肠仔你
You know nothing but sausages
唔准烧呀.
Stop it...
做咩呀！
What do you mean?
我几时至可以扌卜的
When can I make love?
得，弄得我开心，咪比你扌卜啰
Sure, as long as you make me happy
系啰，弄人先至有的扌卜
Yes, you must first make her happy
小妖讲古仔比我听呀
Elf, tell us a story
成日讲话你都唔听
But you won't listen
讲古仔我们听啦
Tell us a story
大众福利嘛
This is for our good
讲啦.
OK, I'll tell you stories...
好啦，听住呀！
OK, listen
从前呢，有个好靓的女人
Long ago, there was a pretty woman
身材好惹火的咼，魔鬼身材， 天使面孑刀
With good figures and face
但系男人同俥做完呢，就冇了下便
But men would lose his dick once making love with her
点解呢，跟住有两兄弟， 个细佬话比阿哥听
Why? There were two brothers, the younger said：
有个好靓的女人， 同俥做完就冇了下便
There's a pretty woman, but one will lose his dick after making love with her
个阿哥唔信，好今晚一于试试先
His brother didn't believe, and tried one night
到了第二朝，个细佬问阿哥
The next day, the younger asked his brother
阿哥.仲系咪度呀？
Brother... is it still there?
俥阿哥唔出声，个细佬觉得奇怪
His brother remained silent, his brother felt strange
再追问阿哥
And kept asking him
阿哥.仲系咪度呀？
Brother... is it still there?
终于呢，俥知道点解阿哥唔答俥
At last, he learnt why his brother remained silent
原来俥阿哥，冇了舌头呀嘛
His brother lost his tongue
你做乜？
What are you doing?
熟啦，趁热食啦
It's cooked, eat it
我讲古仔你食条肠
You eat sausages while I'm telling a story?
好彩唔系我那条
It's lucky not my dick!
咁贱，打到你冇得用呀！
Shit, I must make you impotent
救命.
Help...
唔好打呀，我今晚仲要用个咼
Don't beat it, I need it tonight
Michelle放我.
Michelle, let him...
从前呢，就有两只跳蚤
Long ago, there were two fleas
一只跳蚤呢住在女人的上便
One living on upper part of a woman
一只呢，就住在下便
The other at the bottom part
咁有一日呢两只出来散步， 在肚脐窿相遇
One day they both went for a stroll, and met on the navel
咁下便那只呢就问上便那只啦
The one down there asked the one on the upper part
喂，你上便点呀？
Hey, how is it up there?
几好呀，不过就冻了少少， 你呢，你下便点呀？
Quite good, but a bit cold, what about down there?
几好呀，不过就爠？少少
Quite good, but a bit choky
不如咁啦，我们今晚掉转来睡， 好唔好
Why don't we change our position tonight?
好.
Sure...
跟住呢，过了一晚之后， 第二朝早在肚脐窿度见面咼
And they met again the next morning on the navel
喂，你上便睡成点呀？
How was the high up there?
冇呀，唔知点解， 突然间有东西拍下拍下
While I was sleeping, something kept tapping
好似见到我咁咼
It seemed to see me
俥仲系咁拍，系咁拍， 避迟点呀都比俥拍死呀
It still kept tapping, and I kept jumping
喂，你下便睡成点呀？
And what about down there?
我仲大镬呀，突然间有条大蛇
It's even worse, while I was sleeping, there came big snake
爬了进来，系咁追.追住我呀！
The snake climbed in and chased... me!
还吐口水呀
And then it spit at me!
什么是吐口水呀？
What does spit mean?
Who does spit mean?
吐口水都唔识，等我试比你睇啦
Don't you know? I'll show you
你好衰的，整蛊我，唔睬你呀
Damn you! You fool me?
我去吐口水先啦
I'll go and spit now
咪走呀！
Don't go
唔好跟住呀，唔睬你呀
Don't follow me
我们过那边呀
Let's go there
喂，你有冇带避弹衣呀？
Have you taken condom with you?
我从来都唔用个咼
I never use it
早知你系咁的啦
I know it
唔系呀
Why?
做咩呀，有冇搞错呀咁都跌得
Why, you let it drop?
仲有冇士啤呀？
Is there another one?
冇呀
No!
去洗啰
Go wash it
用咸水呀
With sea water?
唔系点呀
Of course
快点啦，等紧你的
Quick, I'm waiting
得啦.
OK...
除埋条裤至得的
You must take off the trousers too
喂得未呀，咁耐？
Is it done? Why so long?
得啦，我急到赖呀
OK, I must piss
得啦.
Coming...
喂，你估他们去哪边呢？
Where have they gone?
仲驶问？，梗系去了吐口水啦
To spit, of course
你估我吗？对住你眼光光
Only I am as nut as to stare at you
小妖头先讲的故仔好核突呀
The story Elf told was disgusting
唔系吧，睇你头先眼定定， 听到入硒神咼
No, you were deeply interested in it
喂，女仔唔食烟，未必唔系处女
A girl who doesn't smoke might be a virgin
女仔食烟，一定唔系处女
But a girl who smokes can't be virgin
都冇科学根据的
It's not scientific at all
咁你系唔系处女？
Are you a virgin?
有冇搅错呀，乞人憎到死， 唔睬你呀
You're lousy, I won't talk to you
睇你走去边
Where can you go?
仲走
Don't go
好衰的
You're bad
乜你咁衰的，将舌头伸进来？
Why are you so rough as to put your tongue in?
咁先至好玩嘛
This is real fun
十二呀，你点呀？
Sup Yi, what happens to you?
十二.
Sup Yi...
十二呀.你唔好玩啦
Sup Yi... stop fooling
十二呀你做咩溝呀， 唔好吓我呀，唔好再玩啦
Sup Yi, don't scare me, don't play anymore
十二呀请俥走啦，请俥走快点啦
Sup Yi, ask it away, ask it away
十二唔好玩啦，十二
Sup Yi, don't play on
十二呀.唔好啦
Sup Yi, no, don't!
阿东，小妖，救命呀
Tung, Elf, help
小妖
Elf
你做咩呀？
What are you doing?
咩事呀？
What is it?
快点起身啦，救命呀， 十二癫了呀！
Get up and help Sup Yi, he's gone crazy
点会咁的？
How come?
我唔知呀，快去救俥，他快死啦！
I don't know, help him! He's dying
我得张席咋，等我拿番些衫先啦
I only have a mat, I must get my clothes first
快点啦，小妖，十二俥癫？
Be quick, Elf, Sup Yi is mad
快点救俥呀！
Go and help him
你真系冇鬼用的
You're useless
而家先至整亲
You injured at this moment?
激死人啦
It's lousy
救命呀，十二有事，快点救俥呀
Help! Something is happening to Elf, help him
喂，十二有事，去睇俥啦，行啦
Something happens to Elf, go and take a look
十二，你点呀？
Sup Yi, how are you?
快点帮手
Come and help
捉实俥呀
Hold him tight
十二
Sup Yi
十二呀
十二你做乜呀？
What's happened to Sup Yi?
你去边度呀？
Where are you?
快点走呀
Go away
好大力呀
Very strong
十二.你唔好咁呀
Sup Yi... don't be like this
冇计
No way
媪石头扌卜俥啦
Strike him with a stone
唔好呀.你唔好扌卜俥， 你会扌卜死俥的
No... you will kill him this way You must figure it out if not!
点呀！
What to do?
快点念过第二个办法啦
Think of another way now
放低丨日石先啦
Put down the stone first
你念唔念到呀？
Have you any idea?
唔好嘈呀，扌匕起俥先啦
Don't shout! Tie him up first
快点啦
Be quick
放边呀？
Where shall we lay him?
唔好问咁多， 拖埋棵树度扌匕住俥先啦
Drag him to the tree and tie him
捉住俥呀！
Catch him
十二，你点呀，十二，你冇事嘛
Sup Yi, don't be like this
十二，你点呀？
Sup Yi, how are you?
做咩，做咩咁的，咩事呢？
Why, what's on?
那便呀
Over there
Wancy你点呀.冇事呀嘛？
Wancy, how are you? Are you OK?
仲讲乜废话，惗计啦
Don't bullshit, let's think of a way
你们嘈小阵得唔得的， 而家点算呀.
Can you keep quiet? What to do now...
那便有间大屋的，我们扶俥埋去
There's a house over there, let's help him there
好，快
OK, be quick
快啦
Be quick
磨.磨俥两下
Rub... rub it more
撬.定
Hard...
邓.
Tang...
西.
Sai...
顶.
Ting...
两脚一伸
Straight legs
我也不能搞定，你能？
It's fixed! I can't bear but you can Let's drink!
饮番杯，块地卒之搅掂，Cheer
The land problem is fixed, cheers
冇问题.我会尽快带买家 上来写字楼
No problem... I'll bring buyers to your office
你知啦，大陆人下来了好 快上番去的嘛
You know people from China must get back shortly
你在写字楼搅掂份合约， 咁就掂啦嘛
Prepare the contracts and it's fine
这些见到面先再倾啦，好唔好，拜拜
Let's talk when we meet, OK? Bye!
一千五百万
$15 million
呢次有得救啰
It's great for me
何方妖孽？
What devil are you?
你知唔知我系边个， 我尖沙嘴霞姐，你都敢有尔我
Do you know who I am? I am Sister Ha of TST, dare you make use of me?
信唔信我一分钟之内， 媪二百几条靓，劈死你呀
I can call 200 men here in 1 minute and kill you
咁快搅掂的
It's fixed so soon?
你同俥练下膊头，椊下脚指
Rub his shoulders and toes
扌卜多两镬嘛，咁唔长进
Why don't you hit harder?
你知唔知我系边个， 我尖沙嘴霞姐
Do you know I am Sister Ha of TST
点解咁熟的
This is familiar
你都敢有尔，信唔信我一分钟之内
In I minute and kill you
媪二百几条靓劈死你
Dare you make use of me? I can call 200 men
女鬼呀，鬼呀.
Ghost...
翁Sir
Officer Yung
鬼呀.唔好拉脚呀，救命呀
Ghost! Don't pull my legs, help!
我断啦.我只脚断啦
It's broken... my legs are torn off
比番块皮我
Give me back my skin
皮，我冇呀
Skin? I don't have
仲话冇
You said no?
有.咁十皮得唔得？
Yes... is $10 OK?
唔关我事的，我静系带你来呢度咋
It's not my faults, I was only to bring you here
其他的俥同法师搅的咋
The other are all done by the master
你仲讲大话
You lie!
我冇呀，我出去当天发誓都得
I don't, I can swear to Heavens
救命呀.
Help...
鬼呀，有鬼呀
Ghost!
睇你走得去边
Where can you go?
鬼呀.
Ghost...
痛死我，我只脚冇咯
It hurts! My legs are gone!
小心澿呀
Be careful!
快点.
Hurry...
扶俥去棵树那边
Help him to the tree
放低俥先
Put him down first
Wancy点呀？
What about Wancy?
有冇药油呀？
Is there balm?
俥醒啦
She's coming round
媪块布扌匕住俥先啦，快点啦
Find something cloth and bandage him, hurry
咁论尽，等我来啦
Lousy! Let me do it
好痛呀
It hurts
Wancy你冇事嘛？
Wancy, are you OK?
俥包成个史泰龙咁呀
She looks like Stallone now
呢个时候你仲玩
Don't fool now
对唔住呀
Sorry
有人来咼
Someone is coming
乜人来呢？
Who is it?
喂，先生。 。 。
Hey, mister...
我朋友撞亲个头呀， 想借电话打电话报警呀
My friend had her head injured, can we borrow the phone and call for police
先生，边度有电话，乜十问九唔应
Sir, where is there a phone?
你聋定哑呀？
Are you deaf?
喂，电话在那里呀？
Hey, where is the phone?
那边呀
Over there
细路，你咁钟意多管闲事， 我阵间至同你算账
Kid, you like to be busy, I'll come back for you
救命呀，有鬼呀，救命呀.鬼呀.
Help, ghost! Help! Ghost!
妈呀
Jesus
阿姐，唔关我事的，你唔好杀我
It's nothing to do with me, don't kill me
我唔知个马拉法师搅乜鬼， 我仲以为锦衣授魂术呢
I don't know what the master did, I only think
系借你的青春，还番比你的
He's borrowing your youth, this is for you
系我不对，系我唔着， 但系如果你杀了我呢
I'm wrong, I'm to blame, but if you kill me
边个烧金银衣纸， 汽车洋楼番狗比你呢？
No one will burn you things, right?
你放过我啦，我一定烧 硒成副身家比你
Spare me and I'll burn what you need to you
等你做鬼都风风光光， 唔好搅我.
Then you can become a rich ghost, spare me...
喂，起身先至讲啦
Get up first
你唔应承我，我唔起身
I won't get up if you don't promise me
起身啦
Get up
乜原来系你呀？
It's you!
你早点讲比我听呀， 等我个心都跌了出来
You should have told me! You scared me much
仲要我跪你，拜你， 你想玩我呀，你玩我唔起的
You make me kneel and worship you? You are not to fooling me
到底咩事呀？
What is it?
冇事，唔关你事，你多管闲事， 呢度冇你的事
Nothing, none of your business, lousy!
多行不义必自毙， 多行夜路必撞鬼，夜啦睡啦
You'll run into trouble is you go on doing this, go to sleep now
唔系啦
No...
喂，开门呀.我同你玩的咋
Open the door... I was onlyjoking
阿伯，过门都是客， 比我进来饮杯茶，食个饱都得阔
Man, I am more or less your guest, let me in for a cup of tea
开门呀，阿伯，唔系冇你的事
Open the door, man, it's something to do with youl need you now, open the door...
呢度呀
It's here
又系你呀，被你吓鬼死我呀
You again? You scared me to death
你縊我嘛
You scolded me?
原来你系师傅来的，救救我呀
You're Taoist priest? You must help me
班细路而家在哪边？
Where are they kids now?
在那边呀
Over there
去看看
Go and see
师父呀
Master
我搞唔掂的，你去啦， 我同你看屋啦
I can't, you go and I'll watch your house
鬼啊！
小妖
Elf
东
Tung!
十二
Sup Yi
你们在哪呀，Wancy，Lowell？
Where are you? Wancy, Lowell!
点呀？
What shall we do?
呢边呀
This way
码头咁夜冇船啦
There is no boat at this late hour
咁点算呀？
What shall we do then?
冇船啦
No boat!
你走鬼咁鬼快， Michelle都唔见了啦
You ran so quickly that Michelle is left behind
我们番转头媪俥啦
We must go and find her
走吧，去边呀？
Where is she?
好啦，而家媪到件，我们出码头啦
OK, we've found one now, let's go to the pier
你有冇搞错呀，咁我们点呀？
Are you nut? What about me?
咁点呢？
What now?
媪埋他们啦
We must find them back
媪埋两件好走啦
We must go when we find them Wancy
十二，你点呀？
Sup Yi, how are you?
死了？
Dead?
我们走啦
Let's go
未得住呀，Wancy呢？
Not yet! Where's Wancy?
你唔系同俥一齐的咩？
Aren't you with her?
唔系呀，快点媪俥啦
No, let's find her
走啦，你唔走我走啦
I'll leave if you don't go
媪齐人先啦
We must find them all
师傅呀，我而家拮拮下， 帮到你都帮唔到我啦
Master, as I'm crippling, I can't be of help
不如.我就唔.使去啦
What... if... I don't go?
鬼呀.
Ghost...
救命呀，有鬼呀.
Help, ghost...
大师呀，我真系帮唔到你， 盏越帮越忙
Master, I can't help really, I'll make thing worse
唔好呀.
我又肥，又论尽
I am fat and clumsy
救命呀，有鬼呀
Help! There's ghost!
好啦，系咁先，我走啦
OK, I'll leave now
救命呀
Help!
你媪齐班细路去个亭度等我， 唔好走开呀
Find all the kids and wait for me at the pergola
你点呀？
How are you?
死老鬼，你咁钟意多管闲事嘛
Old Bag, must you get involved?
好，我就同你玩？
OK, I'll play with you
死老鬼，我一定唔会放过你的
Old Bag, I won't let you off
老伯.点呀？
Old Man... how are you?
你系咪俾只鬼打伤呀？
Are you injured by the ghost?
唔好讲咁多，过那边抖下
Say no way! Take a rest first
点呀，呢度坐呀
Come and sit here
点呀，你真系冇事嘛？
Are you really OK?
师父，你媪到只女鬼未呀？
Master, have you found the ghost yet?
你快点讲比我听， 你点样惹到俥番？
Tell me how you brought her out!
有个南洋巫师， 用锦衣授魂术帮个女仔换皮
A priest changed a girl's skin with Black magic
咪整死了俥咯
and killed her
邪教巫术，只可以用盐来对付
Black Magic? We can deal with her with salt
咁我们即刻搭船出去媪，好唔好？
Let's take a boat and buy, OK?
你，，屎眼，，生上脑的？
You're just nut!
咁冇盐点算呀，我们今次咪死梗
What shall we do as we have no salt?
有咸味的咁就得的啦
Any salty will do Great, we can find around
快点去啦.
Go quick...
小心呀
Be careful
我陪呀
I'll accompany you here
喂，那边有厨房呀
A kitchen there
周围媪下啦
Look around
媪咸的东西，记住呀
Search for salty thing
知啦
OK
我媪到咸菜干，得唔得？
I've found salty dried vegetable, OK?
我媪到咸酸菜
I've found salty sour vegetable
我媪到成樽豉油
I've found a bottle of soy sauce
我媪到成瓮盐，发达啦
I've found a pot of salt, great
喂，我媪到美极，仲唔腌死个女鬼
I've found Maggie, it can kill the ghost
睇下仲有冇？
Is there anymore?
好啦，差唔多啦，我们走
OK, it's enough, let's go
走，快点啦
Move, hurry
龙虎豹
Blue books?
咸书都系咸咼
Blue books might help
快点呀
Hurry
阿伯
Old Man
好多呀
So much?
够硒咸啦，跟住系边种好呀
It's salty enough, which is best?
唔系叫我系嘛？
You mean me?
呢件事由你引起的，应该由你去
You started all this, it should be you
师父呀，我又跛又细胆，唔得咼
Master, I'm crippling and timid
唔去得唔得呀？
Can I stay behind?
唔去，唔去打到你去
We'll beat you until you will go
唔好打呀.
Don't beat me...
你避得一时唔避得一世， 你唔引俥出来
You can't keep away from her forever, if you don't attract her out
我冇办法捉到俥咼， 你知唔知道？
I can't catch her, you know?
我而家真系好惊呀
I am very afraid
你唔驶惊，呢道符可以保护到你？
Don't panic, this spell can protect you
我跛的嘛，我见到俥我都 追唔到俥啦，系唔系呀？
I'm crippled, I can't chase after her, right?
咁我而家点呀？
What shall I do now?
呢条红绳绑住你，你见到女鬼阵呢
I'm trying you with this red thread, when the ghost appears
你就拉三下，咁我就会出来救你啦
You must pull three times and I'll help you
我点见到俥呀？
How can I see her?
呢个测鬼追踪器， 会带你去媪俥出来
This detector can bring you to her
测鬼呀？
Detector?
去啦，快？呀
Go now
掂唔掂的？
Will it work?
掂的啦
Yes, it will
仲唔去，小心点呀
Go now, be careful
大师呀，你睇住我呀
Master, you must protect me
得啦，行啦
OK, go now
去啦
Go
我拉三下就来救我啦
Go and help if I pull three times
救命呀
Help!
挣点俾你吓到线
You nearly scared me to death
来呀
Come on
来呀，有符唔惊你的
Come on, I don't fear you as I have a spell
只鬼来啦
Here come the ghost
见到只女鬼边个淋先呀？
Who splashes the ghost if it comes?
是但啦，执生呀
Anyone can do, be smart!
快点快点
Hurry...
条绳剪断了，梗系走佬了啦
The thread is cut, it must have gone away
条绳咸味好重，应该是上面咼
It smells salty, should be up there
我们上去媪
Let's go and find up there
两条路咼，咁点呀？
Two paths? Which to take?
三个男仔行呢便啦
Three boys get this path
老伯呀，我陪你
Old Man, I'll stay with you
跟我来
Follow me
你去边度呀？
Where have you been?
睇你个死样呀，惊到面都白硒
Look how pale you are
你做咩呀，仲玩，线的
What are you doing? You nut!
去媪阿伯
Go and find Old Man
喂，阿伯呀，我们在那里啊
Old Man, we're here
快上来啦，媪到四眼佬啦
Get up here, we've found him
他在这里，上来啦
He's here, come up
我们媪到俥啦，原来俥作弄我们
We've found him! He's hiding here
小心呀，俥系鬼，媪东西泼俥啦
Watch out! He's ghost, splash him
俥系鬼上身，他们唔够打的， 我们上去帮俥？
He's being possessed, they're not up to him, let's go and help them
开唔倒盖呀
The lid is stuck
走呀.救命呀.
Go... help!
十二呀，快拉住藤呀，我扯你上？
Sup Yi, hold the rattan, I'll pull you up
阿东呀
Tung
快来救我呀！
Come and help me
咸书，问你惊未！
Blue books can kill you
泼俥
Splash
快点泼俥啦
Splash at once
帮拖
Help them
放手呀.
Hands off...
衰人，你快点放手呀
Hands off at once
我们去沙滩
Let's go to the beach
救命呀
Help!
救咩命呀，到地啦，吓傻了咩
Help? You're on the ground already
快点啦，快点呀
Be quick...
老伯，你点呀，跳啦
Old Man, how are you? Jump
咁高，点跳呀，喂，等埋我们呀
I can't as it's so high up, wait for us
快点跳啦，跳啦，追到了啦
Jump now! It's almost here
捉住俥啦
Catch it
跳啦
Jump now!
咪走呀
Don't go
快点.
Hurry...
等埋我呀
Wait for me
走快点啦
Run for life
去找咸水
Get sea water
喂，快点啦，我顶唔顺湿啦
Hurry, I can't hold on
快点
Be quick
漏Q硒添
It's leaking
快点啦，除条裤啦
Hurry, take off the trousers
你条红色裤嘛，拿来兜水？
Yours is red, use it to take water
喂，他们除裤，我们除乜呀？
They have trousers, what do we have?
除胸围啦
Let's take our bras off
拿.
Take it...
拿水？
Get water
又漏啦
It's leaking
走先啦，走先啦
Let's run away
漏硒啦
It's spilt off
小心点呀
Be careful
小心行呀，漏硒啦
Watch out, it's spilt out
含多啖水添
Get some in the mouth
咪住咪住，我又含啖先
Hold it, I'll get some too
快点呀，快点呀
Hurry...
仆卜你个家铲， 快点惗过第二个办法啦！
Damn you! Think of another way now
快点呀
Be quick
快点啦，你学咩人讲点呀， 漏硒啦！
What are you bullshit? It's all leaked
快点
Be quick
乜你咁鬼蠢湿
Why are you so foolish?
快点呀
Faster
来紧
Coming
快点，泼俥，泼俥呀
Splash at it, quick
帮手，帮手拉呀
Help me, pull it
快点唔好衰呀
Be quick, hold on
来啦，得啦
Coming, it's done
我媪到个泵呀，潜下去
I've found a pump
快点帮忙
Come and help
那个泵俾我
Get me the pump
那条喉呢
Get a hose
我行去前面呀
I'll go to the front
我们去
Let's go
唔够长呀，长点添呀
It's not long enough, longer
行去前面度啦
Get to the front
收到
Got it
点呀？
What now?
再行前澿
Get a bit more to the front
仲未够长呀，快点啦，放长点啦
Still not long enough! Hurry, roll more out
得啦
OK
尽硒的啦
It's the longest now
尽硒啦
The longest now
拉埋点添呀
Pull it a bit near
冇水啦
It's going to break, get near
唔掂啦，抽唔到水呀
No way, it can't pump water
去带过条长点的水喉来呀
Get a longer hose here
快点，拿水喉来啦
Be quick, get it here
你顶住先，拉实俥
Hold on, pull it
长喉来啦，点呀？
Here is the longer hose, what now?
行出点
A bit out
老豆，我就来顶唔顺啦，整丨日铁呀
Father, I can't hold on
快点呀，老豆呀
Be quick, dad
快点呀
Be quick
射俥
Splash at it
点呀？
How is it?
射死俥.
Splash at it...
条尸葬在边度呀？
Where was the body buried?
你知唔知呀？
Do you know?
阿伯，我知道在边度呀
I know where it is
在边呀？
Where?
那便呀
There
你们继续顶住条尸呀
Hold on with the body
系呢度呀
It's here
青竹葬？
'Bamboo Burial'?
冇事啦，俥醒番啦
It's OK, coming round now
俥醒啦，扶俥起身先啦
Help her up now
俥块面明明系烂的，点解冇事了
Her face is ruined but it's OK now?
俥鬼上身先会咁的， 而家破了锦衣授魂术
She was possessed, now that I've broken the spirit
俥冇事啦
She'll be fine
咁而家点做好呀？
What shall we do now?
而家送俥返去我屋企度先
Take her to my house first
行啦
Move
小心点呀
Be careful
阿光，你做乜呀？
Kwang, what are you doing?
大师，俥做乜呀？
Master, what happens to him?
俥不过系惊慌过度， 我们扶俥番去先啦
He's too scared, let's help him back
好呀！起身啦
OK! Get up
做咩呀？
Why?
行啦！
Move
细路，下次再来离岛的时候
Kids, next time when you come to a remote place
唔好再搅神搅鬼啦， 对你们冇益的
Don't fool around again, as it's dangerous
番去俾心机读书啦
Go and study hard
如果有时间，咁你们约埋 一齐来探望我啦咼
Come and see me if you have time
知唔知我屋企在边度呀？
Do you know where my house is?
知道
Yes
好啦，再见啦
OK, bye
我们走啦
We'll leave now
拜拜，老伯
Bye, Old Man
好声呀
Be careful
拜拜.
Bye...
你保重啦
Take care of yourself
我们会来探你的
We'll come to see you soon
拜拜.
Bye...
站在这里，唔好有尔呀
Stand there! Don't move!
快点食
Eat fast
这些是泥，唔食得的，唔好食啦
This is soil, you mustn't eat it
行啦
Move!
呢度
Here